karaokeparty.com 2014-04-19

# KaraokeParty.com - Free Online Karaoke Party Game

To use KaraokeParty you don’t have to register or give up any personal information. We explicitly ask for your personal information when we want it. 

In order to register as a member at KaraokeParty you need to give us your email address, an alias, and age. 

**Why we collect personal information**   
We collect your personal information because it helps us deliver a superior level of customer service. It enables us to give you convenient access to our products and services and focus on categories of greatest interest to you. In addition, your personal information helps us keep you posted on the latest product announcements, special offers, and events that you might like to hear about. 

**The way we use Personal Information**   
Your email address is used by KaraokeParty to send information about news at KaraokeParty and will not be handed out to third party vendors. The information about age is mainly used to identify minors that need to get permission from their parents or legal guardian to become members at KaraokeParty. (Minors in the US are defined as children under 13, in non-US minors are defined as under 16 of age.) 

We reserve the right to collect and disclose (to our affiliates and to non-affiliate third parties) user behaviour and Personal Information to the extent permitted by applicable law, as specifically restricted below or in the Terms of Use. Notwithstanding anything to the contrary in this Privacy Policy or elsewhere, we reserve the right at all times to disclose any information as necessary to satisfy any applicable law (including, without limitation, the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act), regulation, legal process, law enforcement requests, demands by parties claiming your infringement of their rights or governmental request, to edit, refuse to post or remove any information or materials, in whole or in part, in our sole discretion; or to act in an emergency to protect someone’s safety or legal rights. 

We have no control over third parties to whom you may give Personal Information through the use of KaraokeParty. We use the information you provide about yourself or others to complete the transaction for which the information is intended. Such transactions may include: administering a service, such as email, search, advertising sales, ecommerce; completing an order; replying to support requests; or contacting you if you have granted us permission to do so. 

We may also use personally identifiable user information to provide targeted content and commerce opportunities to users based on their demographic and behavioral information. 

Finally, we never use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways or for reasons unrelated to the ones described above without also providing an opportunity to opt-out or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses. 

**How we protect your personal information**   
We take precautions — including administrative, technical, and physical measures — to safeguard your personal information against loss, theft, and misuse, as well as unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration, and destruction. 

**Cookie**   
We may place a text file called a "cookie" in the browser files of your computer. The cookie enables us to collect information about your visits to KaraokeParty. We may use this information to enhance your KaraokeParty experience and may share some information with our members, vendors, sponsors or others. 

You can turn off the cookie function in your web browser, then you won't be able to register as a member or log in. 

**Third Party Cookies**   
We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. This may also include whether you interacted with content on the site(s). If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, click [here](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).
